Or Zarhi

Full-Stack Developer

About Me

I'm an experienced software developer with 1.5 years of experience in the industry and a deep passion for programming. Throughout my career, I'm always looking for ways to improve my skills and stay on top of the latest technologies.

Experience

Full-Stack Developer

Maxsoft company Aug 2022 to present A Full Stack developer at a professional software company. Worked on several projects for various customers. Developed and maintained code with assorted tools, such as: Node.js, .net, mongoDB, Sql, JavaScript and React.

Computer Science Tutor

Zefat College

Jan 2023 to present

Teaching C#, Data structures and Algorithms courses. Letter of recommendation

Full-Stack Developer

Codeo company Jan 2022 to Jul 2022 I worked as Full Stack Developer. I developed and maintained code. I had the chance to work with: Node.js, .net, JavaScript and React.

Education

Kinneret College

Nov 2019 to Jun 2023

Practical Software Engineer Student

93 GPA

Skills

Node.js, Express.js, NoSQL, React, Remix, Tailwind

Military Service

Division 319

Feb 2016 to Oct 2018

I managed other soldiers, took care of orders and supplies.

Contact

052-363-8638

www.linkedin.com/in/or-zarhi



or.zarhi11@gmail.com



https://github.com/orzarhi